[Music]
[Música]
and they were throwing a lot of [ __ ] at him
y le estuvieron tirando mucha [__]
god I didn't put much into the salt or
dios me no me puse mucho en el sal se o
that because we were with I don't
de eso porque estábamos con no me
remember what things yet but he hammock
acuerdo qué cosas todavía pero se hamaca
license or not
carnet o no
canet or not
canet o no
here it's my turn to put in it has the name of a
acá me toca meto tiene nombre de
Doraemon character I put it in
personaje de doraemon la meto
and
y
ugt
ugt
[ __ ] that I put in streaming today in
camelo que meto en streaming today en
yesterday is the best or streams carrer
yesterday is the best o streams carrer
show these guys are streaming websites
show estos chicos son webs de streaming
air carrier sexto reviews showroom play
air carrier sexto reviews showroom play
for me
for me
and I tried rifai
y yo intenté rifai
ibai father ando khan aqa mico is called
ibai padre ando khan aqa mico se llama
hecho here it's my turn to put in in total that he has
hecho acá me toca meto en total que ha
received a lot of hate and it's going to go from
recibió muchísimo odio y va a ir por
the French man and then
parte de los franceses tío y entonces
here apparently he's been there he talks
aquí por lo visto pues lleva ahí habla
a little about what happened in these days in
un poco de lo que pasó en estos días en
the last hours I have
las últimas horas
read the four also that they have
he leído a los cuatros también que han
said that yesterday there was a lack of
dicho que ayer faltaba un poco de
representation from other streams
representación por parte de otros stream
it's from other communities also even
es de otras comunidades también incluso
from girls I people the truth is that the
de chicas yo gente la verdad que el
album that they thought of the public okay okay okay okay okay
disco que pensaban de público vale vale
this about the third of the album
vale vale vale esto de terna del disco
with a fact is this is because the fans
con un hecho es esto es porque los fans
of the clash have been throwing it
del choque han estado tirándole
because the  camera moves alone dude
porque la cámara se mueve sola tío
you see how the camera moves alone on a
veis como la cámara se mueve sola en un
shitty tripod that moves alone I
trípode de [__] que se mueve solo
always have things more to the guy I'm
siempre tengo las cosas más al tío estoy
tired I'm tired god willing be a
cansado estoy cansado dios quiera se me
salsa dancer calm down
salsero tranquilo
family this is because the
familia esto es porque los fans del
chocas fans were yesterday throwing it in his face and
chocas estaban ayer echándole en cara y
bye
bye
that they hadn't invited chocas to the redit thing
que no habían invitado a lo de redit al
okay and this is the explanation that
vale y esta es la explicación que
they were device the only person
estaban device la única persona que
left was really get surf and I
quede realmente fue consigue surf y yo
thought that whoever wanted to was coming and going
pensaba que iba entrando y saliendo
okay I also thought that in
quien quería vale también pensé que de
some way it was a little uncomfortable for
alguna manera era un poco incómodo para
some stream in that call because there
algún stream en esa llamada porque
were 14 of us and there was even one time I
éramos 14 e incluso había alguna vez me
went crazy I don't know if it happened to you
volví a la cabeza loca no sé si os pasó
you know that there were 14 of us screaming like
sabes que éramos 14 gritando como
real gorillas and I understand that for
auténticos gorilas y entiendo que por
example if I Juan didn't like being on
ejemplo si yo juan no le molaba estar
the call for a long time because he wanted to be more
mucho la llamada porque quería estar más
arroyo chill with his streaming not with 14
arroyo chill con su streaming no con 14
people going crazy and then of
personas volviéndose locos y entonces
course there were maybe several streams it's because they did
claro igual hubo varios stream es porque
n't want to join there because the normal thing
no se querían unir ahí porque lo normal
is to be divided into calls of 4 or 5
es estar divididos en llamadas de 4 o 5
people and we honestly didn't
personas y nosotros la verdad que no
get 14 fish 14 people the record
metimos 14 pescado 14 personas el disco
people are  crazy and more if it's
gente es una locura y más si está
comanche that comanche counts for 10-2
comanche que comanche cuenta por 10-2
we were 200 okay and chop crazy chef
éramos 200 vale y picar chef loco
were comanche and crazy cancer we were
estaban comanche y cáncer loco éramos
400 because 14 a little bit like that well ok
400 porque 14 a un poquito así bien ok
perez who was karcher excited that
pérez que estaba karcher excitado que
cat was saying eat my dick every
cat se decía comedme la [__] cada
minute me that kid yesterday didn't surpass
minuto yo ese chaval ayer no sobrepasó
the truth
la verdad
and then he was with stains that I stained it
y luego estaba con manchas que lo manche
is the pure show
es el puro show
and the whole project that just like thinking
y todo el proyecto que igual que pensar
the album didn't have many people I
el disco no tenía mucha gente yo me
put the album in now yesterday and I was
metía el disco ahora ayer y yo me iba
meeting new people I was duck I
encontrando gente nueva yo estaba pato
was already here there were a lot of people
estaba ya aquí estaba un montón de gente
that I didn't even know was doing this
que yo ni sabía que estaba haciendo esto
but I met them and I said [ __ ]
pero me los encontré y dije de [__]
great I mean between whoever wants the
madre o sea que entre quien quiera la
truth and friends the truth to say is
verdad y amigos la verdad que decir es
that in fact I am on that album I think I do
que de hecho yo estoy en ese disco creo
n't know if I do
no sé si
n't know if it's the same one I'm on
no sé si es el mismo en el que yo estoy
but in fact I am on that album I
pero de hecho yo estoy en ese disco
don't have the restorer of discord yet
no tengo todavía el restaurador de la
okay why have I
vale por qué
received the greatest amount of hate and
he recibido la mayor cantidad de odio y
harassment that I have received in the 8 years
de acoso que he recibido en los 8 años
that I have been doing things  the internet has
que llevo haciendo cosas de internet ha
been an absolute outrage
sido una auténtica barbaridad
for me it has surpassed all limits
para mí ha superado todos los límites
instead of today they have seen on the internet I have
que en vez de hoy han visto en internet
honestly been
sinceramente
shocked the truth look at the
me he quedado impactado la verdad mira
things that have happened to me on the internet they
que me han pasado cosas en internet
have insulted me they have said everything to me too
me han insultado me ha dicho de todo
many comment of course many
también muchos comentan por supuesto
many more good than bad
muchos muchísimos más buenos que malos
but yesterday was an outrage I mean it's
pero lo de ayer fue una barbaridad o sea
not a joke yes maybe I have had
no es broma si a lo mejor he tenido
more than half a million mentions and
más de medio millón de menciones y
wishing me death of everything a little no
deseándome la muerte de todo un poco no
son of a [ __ ] disgusting fat all the
hijo de [__] asqueroso gordo todos los
insults that you can think of I mean
insultos que se os puedan ocurrir o sea
a real beast in fact last
una auténtica animalada de hecho ayer
night I didn't look at my phone I mean I
por la noche yo no miré el móvil o sea
was with
estaba con
con saba who is the sporting director
con saba que es el director deportivo
of the team I am chatting for a while and I fell
del equipo estoy charlando un rato y me
asleep this morning he has a ton
dormí hoy por la mañana tiene un montón
of things to do he has had several
de cosas que hacer ha tenido varias
meetings because this week is going to be
reuniones porque esta semana va a ser
a very important week and I don't know
una semana muy importante tal y no sé
what and the truth is that he looks at his phone very little
qué y la verdad que mira muy poco el
but the times that I have looked it has
móvil pero las veces que he mirado ha
been an absolute outrage I mean my
sido una auténtica barbaridad o sea mis
mentions are constantly with
menciones son constantemente con gente
French people and it no longer bothers me that they
francesa y ya no me molesta que me
insult me ​​and that they don't stop because they are not
insulten y que no paren porque no están
stopping really yes  this yes what I have
parando de verdad si este si esto que he
received I would have received what type
recibido yo lo hubiese recibido qué tipo
of
de
audience will this guy have
audiencia tendrá el tío de che
each goal
cada meta
this is the payment
este es el pago
and I
y
think the turkey makes
creo que hace el pavo
videos
videos
what does this man usually do
qué es lo que suele hacer este hombre
all the videos
todos los vídeos
he puts thumbnails
le pone miniaturas
on the
a la
'pole' thumbnail the videos of tweets
'pole' miniatura los vídeos de tuits
or in other words what he does in playing will
o sea lo que hace en jugar
have a type of audience a little girl
tendrá un tipo de audiencia un poco niña
is the best that has been put to
está lo mejor que se haya puesto a
look there it goes there I am not
buscar ahí va ahí no
going to tell you things but the place
voy a decirles cosas pero el sitio sea
was
fue
incredible incredible incredible the one that
increíble increíble increíble la que
fell but carto realize that almost it would be the
cayó pero carto date cuenta que casi que
same
sería lo mismo
so it would be the same of someone who will
así que sería lo mismo de alguien que se
fight shalkan and that
peleará shalkan y que también habrá
things will also have arrived I imagine from the part of the
llegado cosas me imagino por parte de la
Spanish community or not we do not know
comunidad española o no no lo sabemos
to vícam eto'o is the organizer of
a vícam eto'o es el organizador de
carmina corp which is the rival of today
carmina corp que es el rival de hoy
[Music] I
[Música]
think that in all the sides there are
creo que en todos los bandos hay gente
toxic people because surely the result of
tóxica pues seguramente el resultado de
this one will be because that sense camet west will
éste será porque ese sentido camet oeste
have a lot of very toxic audience
tendrá mucha audiencia muy tóxica
this jump that the camera moves
este salto que la cámara se mueva
you notice it or am I crazy
ustedes lo notáis o soy yo estoy loco
[Music]
[Música]